let quiz = [{

        question: "Pipe A can fill the tank in 12 hours and pipe B can fill the tank in 20 hours. A third pipe C empties the tank in 30 hours. If all pipes are opened together then find the time taken to fill the tank completely?",
        option: [
            "13",
            "10",
            "12",
            "8"
        ],
        answer: 2,
    }, {

        question: "Two pipes A and B can fill a tank in 90 minutes and 75 minutes respectively. There is also an outlet C. If all the three pipes are opened together, the tank is full in 50 minutes, how much time will be taken by C to empty the full tank?",
        option: [
            "210 minutes",
            "90 minutes",
            "112 minutes",
            "225 minutes"
        ],
        answer: 4,

    }, {

        question: "One pipe can fill a tank in 50 hours. Due to a leak the total time taken to fill the tank was 60 hours. How much time will the leak take to empty a half-filled tank?",
        option: [
            "120 hours",
            "80 hours",
            "150 hours",
            "180 hours"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {

        question: "A pipe can fill a tank in 10 minutes and another can fill the tank in 20 minutes. If both the pipe are kept open, then in how much time tank will be completely full?",
        option: [
            "6.67 min",
            "10 min",
            "8 min",
            "6 min"
        ],
        answer: 1,
    }, {

        question: "Two pipes A and B can empty a tank in 24 hours and 36 hours respectively while another pipe C can fill the same tank in 6 hours. All three pipes opened for 8 hours and then both A and B is closed find the total time in which the tank will be filled.",
        option: [
            "360 min",
            "480 min",
            "540 min",
            "560 min"
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },


    {

        question: "Tap M alone can fill the tank in 5 hours and tap N alone can fill the tank in 15 hours. If both opened till half of the tank gets filled and then tap N is closed. Total time required to fill the tank is â€“",
        option: [
            "32/13 hours",
            "35/9 hours",
            "35/8 hours",
            "32/7 hours"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {

        question: "A tank consist of one inlet and one outlet pipe. The Inlet pipe fills the tank in 10 hours and the outlet pipe empties the tank in 15 hours. Find the time taken to fill the tank when both pipes are open together.",

        option: [
            "10 hours",
            "15 hours",
            "30 hours",
            "25 hours"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {

        question: "Pipe Q can fill a tank 4 times faster than pipe X. If both the pipes are opened together and they fill the tank in 36 minutes then find the time taken by pipe X to fill the tank alone.",
        option: [
            "150 minutes",
            "145 minutes",
            "180 minutes",
            "130 minutes"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {

        question: "Three pipes A, B and C were opened to fill a tank. Working alone A, B and C requires 12 minutes, 15 minutes and 20 minutes respectively. Another pipe D, which is outlet pipe, can empty the fully filled tank in 30 minutes working alone. What is the total time taken to fill the tank if all the pipes are simultaneously opened?",
        option: [
            "3 minutes",
            "8 minutes",
            "6 minutes",
            "5 minutes"
        ],
        answer: 3,
    }, {

        question: "Pipes A and B together take 20 hours, B and C together take 15 hours, and C and A together take 12 hours to fill a tank. In what time will the tank be filled if all 3 pipes work together?",
        option: [
            "10 hours",
            "15 hours",
            "12.5 hours",
            "5 hours"
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
];